Whatever it is
放轻松
Let me come
我帮你录像吗？
Sure, Well
好 那么
You are?
你这是？
Are you sure?
你确定？
No, but that's true
不，但这是真的
Is this a joke? -No.
-这是个玩笑吗？-不
Does it look like she's joking?
她看起来像在开玩笑吗？
So good for you
真好啊
我的家人对我出柜的反应
妈妈：觉得她做不了姥姥了
表妹：在脸书上大肆宣传
爸爸：为我选女朋友的眼光骄傲
我如何正式告知我的爸爸
我出柜这件事
I am not gay
我不是纯粹的同性恋
Just a little bit of a gay
我只是有那么一点特质
I believe it guaranteed it certainly attracted to women
我确信就这么一点
它也肯定吸引了别的女孩
我好紧张
What does that say?
这说明了什么？
I'm Bi?
“我是双性恋”？
Are you serious?
真的吗？
I can't read it
我看不懂
It's okay, it's okay baby
没关系，没事的宝贝
我的父母是如此支持我！
我深爱着他们！
It's okay, you don't have to be…
没关系，你不必
I'm Bi. - Is that what it says?
-“我是双”-是这么说的吗？
It's okay, why are you so upset? It's okay
没关系，你为什么这么难过？没事的
Mom, I love you
妈妈，我爱你
It's okay. Were you scared?
真的没关系 你在害怕吗？
好兄弟：妈妈我是同性恋
其他兄弟：我也是
妈妈：看在上帝的面子上，
这个家中有一个人喜欢女孩吗？
我：
妈妈：不
Why would you do that?
你为什么要这么做？
Why would you be a gay?
你为什么要再做一次？
Cause I am, do you love me still?
因为我认真的，你还爱我吗？
You're so dumb
你怎么这么傻
What?
什么？
Am I suppose to pretend that I didn't know?
我应该假装我不知道吗？
我的家人对出柜的反应
我妈
我弟
我爸为我不会怀孕而高兴
因为一些家人们认为一个阶段过去了
在此我做一个2020年的重申
I'm still gay! Ohhh!
我还是同性恋！
我还！是！同性恋！
我：你们听懂了吗？
我：你听歌词了吗？
你是女同性恋吗？
我找我的室友跟我一起拍视频
我早就知道你是女同性恋了
I gotta tell you something
我得告诉你一件事
What?
什么？
You can't be mad
你不能生气
What?
什么？
I'm gay
我是同性恋
I knew yes was gay when he was five years old
我知道，你五岁的时候就是同性恋
你是同性恋吗？
不是啊，怎么了？
等等我刚问你什么了？
你是同性恋吗？
哦，是的...你怎么知道的？
woc 真的吗
2020年 出柜快乐
Doesn't call me back right now you better be joking
现在不要给我回电话 你最好是在开玩笑
I do not want to gay friend
我不想同性恋朋友!
I do not want to gay friends
我不想！跟同性恋做朋友！
stop watching and tik-tok
别刷抖音了
you're not a lesbian
你不是女同性恋
信不信由你
当我兄弟得知我出柜
跟着歌词一起唱
她这次听懂了